forexoptimum.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy | Forex Optimum

Forex Optimum Company is serious about security and privacy. The safety and security of the personal data of our Сustomers, both future and present and our visitors is our priority.  
Providing services to its customers, we collect and store their personal data. That is why we would like to acquaint you with the privacy policy, which will be also applicable in relation to you, if you decide to use, or use the services of our company.  
This policy only applies to websites that are directly supported by ForexOptimum and does not apply to other organizations and individuals, to which we may link to in our banners or links on our Web sites. When you open and maintain any accounts at ForexOptimum company, both live and demo, we collect your personal information solely for business purposes. During the work, we can receive from you the following confidential information:

1\. Personal information you provide in the statements, questionnaires and forms for opening account: your full name, address, date of birth, passport details, occupation and position;  
2\. Financial information, such as your investment experience;  
3\. Documents required for your identification: passport, bills to pay utilities and / or bank statement or constituent documents of your the company;  
4\. Documents provided by you to confirm the transfer of funds: money orders, bank statements, copies of credit cards, etc.

The Company may use your personal information to:  
1\. Verify your identity;  
2\. Promptly process your trading and non-trading operations;  
3\. Promptly inform you about expanding the list of services and products provided by the Company, which we believe may interest you;  
4\. Provide you with other services related to your trading account;  
5\. Maintain a valid registration database of your client accounts;  
6\. Analyze statistical data, to offer you products and services of higher quality;

### Cookies

Cookies — a small piece of information sent by a web server to store on your computer user as a file, so that during your next-use web site can retrieve this information. This file is sent each time to the web server in the http-request when you try to open a page of the appropriate site. Cookies may be used on some pages of our website to provide you with quick and easy access. If you do not wish to receive Cookies, the majority of web browsers allow you to reject them, at the same time allowing you to visit our site without any restrictions. Cookies are not used to identify our visitors.

### Third parties

The Company has the right to disclose your identity information to subsidiaries / affiliates, agents of the Company, companies or other trusted organizations and individuals (hereinafter — the trustee) only for the purpose of processing your trading and non-trading orders. The company guarantees observance of this Policy by the trustees and the adoption of the said persons the necessary measures to protect the confidential information of the client company. The company has the right to provide confidential information about the Client’s personal data to third parties who are not trustees, only if an official request comes from administrative and / or judicial bodies. By using Information when registering an account with the Company, you agree to the use of personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. ForexOptimum also has the right to give some identifying information about customers to its regional representatives to provide a complete and quality service.

### Security and Protection

The company practices responsible approach to the security of personal data of the Customer. The Company is taking all necessary measures to protect your privacy, including maintaining strict security standards for the exchange of confidential information within the company and the use of leading technology storage security data. To make a payment with a credit card, you fill out the form at the processing center website. To exclude the possibility of using these data, it is transferred to the Company ForexOptimum in a shortened version over a secure connection.

### Transmission of information to regulatory authorities

In exceptional circumstances, the Company may disclose your personal information to third parties if it is permitted or required by norms of applicable law or other regulations.

### Refusal to provide information

You are not obliged to provide us with any personal information that we may have to ask you. However, failure to provide information may result in our inability to open or maintain your account or to provide you with services. Since we are working hard to ensure that all information provided by you is accurate, complete and up to date, you can significantly help us in this regard, promptly notifying us of any changes to your Contact Information.

If you have any questions relating to this policy, we will be happy to answer to them by email: cs@forexoptimum.com
